A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Photographs, RG 1044 FA1768
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Photographs, RG 1044
1953-1967
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Brothers Fund
Camp, John R. (1909-)
FA1768
0.76 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged material is available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This record group contains photographs, primarily associated with the RBF's West Africa Program.
Arrangement
As received.
Photographs
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs, 1957-1963; 1044; 0.76 Cubic Feet
  Photographs
  - West Africa Program
    - Robert I. Fleming photos, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - John R. Camp Survey, Snapshots, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - John R. Camp Survey, Album, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 266)
    - John R. Camp Survey, Album, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - Ghana: Poultry Breeding, 1960 December (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - Ghana: Water Project, Pakro Dam, 1959 December (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - Ghana: Water Project, Pakro Dam, 1959 December (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - Nigeria: Electrical Assembly Project, 1962 March (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - Nigeria: Housing, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - Iron and Steel, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - Nigeria: Textiles, 1963 March (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - President, William M. Dietel (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - Staff (Box 22, Folder 276)